{
    "subject": "\u00c9ric_Rochant",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "The_Patriots__film_",
    "human_readable": "\u00c9ric Rochant created the film The Patriots.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9110633134841919,
            "question": "What film was created by \u00c9ric Rochant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8405789136886597,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by \u00c9ric Rochant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.794773280620575,
            "question": "What did \u00c9ric Rochant create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6997650265693665,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of a film made by \u00c9ric Rochant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6985026001930237,
            "question": "Name a film directed by \u00c9ric Rochant."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6316052079200745,
            "question": "Is there a movie called The Patriots?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6117087602615356,
            "question": "Who directed the film The Patriots?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5780783295631409,
            "question": "Is The Patriots a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5051818490028381,
            "question": "What kind of work did \u00c9ric Rochant produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3239915668964386,
            "question": "Who is the director behind The Patriots?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=\u00c9ric Rochant created the film The Patriots.",
            "html": "yago_12212_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work did \u00c9ric Rochant produce?",
            "html": "yago_12212_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is The Patriots a movie?",
            "html": "yago_12212_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the film The Patriots?",
            "html": "yago_12212_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12212_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12212_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12212_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12212_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12212_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12212_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12212_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12212_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12212_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12212_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. According to the texts, \u00c9ric Rochant is mentioned as the director of the film \"Les Patriotes\" (also known as \"The Patriots\"), and the context suggests that he created the movie."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Eric Rochant is indeed the filmmaker who created the movie \"The Patriots.\" This is supported by phrases such as \"In his third and most accessible feature, \u2018The Patriots,\u2019 rising French filmmaker Eric Rochant continues to explore the themes of political commitment and personal integrity\" and \"Cannes Film Festival 1994 (In Competition)\u2013In his third and most accessible feature, The Patriots,\" which clearly attribute the film's creation to Eric Rochant."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}